<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ghost on Kelly&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://kellyalvarenga.com/author/ghost/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ghost on Kelly&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 04:08:15 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kellyalvarenga.com/author/ghost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top of the world</title>
      <link>https://kellyalvarenga.com/article/topoftheworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 16:38:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kellyalvarenga.com/article/topoftheworld/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar</title>
      <link>https://kellyalvarenga.com/article/gunnar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 04:08:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kellyalvarenga.com/article/gunnar/</guid>
      <description>Gunnar is one half of the deadly duo Gunnar and Charlotte, they love nothing more than to run around chasing birds and each other.
He was born on October 29, 2019, he is a solid liver brown with only a sliver of white fur on his neck he was purchased when he was 3 months old from an ad on Craigslist it read &amp;ldquo;Weimerainer mix puppies $100&amp;rdquo;. The owner threw in his sister Charlotte for only $50 more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Juan, Puerto Rico</title>
      <link>https://kellyalvarenga.com/gallery/puerto-rico/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 01:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kellyalvarenga.com/gallery/puerto-rico/</guid>
      <description>We Stayed in Puerto Rico from July 1st 2021 till July 30 2021, visited El Yunque national park and a few other touristy things.
The Airbnb we got was in Rio Piedras which could be &amp;lsquo;ok&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;not ok at all&amp;rsquo; luckily we landed on the better side of that neighborhood, overall really enjoyed my stay here.
Some of the things we learned in PR:
-You can rent a moving van cheaper than you can rent a compact car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kellyalvarenga.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kellyalvarenga.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Greetings,
This is a page made for Kelly to post her pictures in a secure serverless static website. this is the second attempt, read first attempt below;
1st attempt:
-created static files using hugo https://themes.gohugo.io/: -uploaded them to Github -used AWS codebuild to run a sync to an s3 bucket (later removed this) -purchased domain -created records in Route53 -created Cloudfront distribution &amp;ndash;note: need to ensure used rest api endpoint rather than usding the bucket to serve the files -used lambda@Edge function to create a redirect for the uri(see:https://dev.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
